Woradanue Nakdee (Pleng)

(+66) 95 959 8468 plengwn@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/plengnakdee/ https://plengnakdee.github.io/

SUMMARY

Even though my previous experience was in film and TV production, I decided to change my career after learning how to code. I enjoy the analytical and problem solving aspects that came with coding. I'm currently a graduate student in computer science and particularly interested in deep learning. I can work in both team and individual settings, with strong work ethic and drive to success.

TECHNICAL PROFILE

Languages: Python, SQL, Solidity Libraries: PyTorch, Keras, OpenCV Other: Microsoft Office Suite, Keynote

EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant Jan 2019 - Present

National Institute of Development Administration

- Course title: Image Analytics
- Evaluate and grade student assignments.
- Prepare and proctor examinations.
- Explain coding exercises.
- Distribute classroom materials.

Associate Producer June 2015 - Nov 2017

IFA Media

- Research and develop new documentary or TV format.
- Manage logistics of production.
- Manage post-production legal documents.

Co Producer Jan 2015 - Feb 2015

Mono Technology Public Company Limited

- Co-produce foreign news show.
- Search for news content.
- Coordinate in studio.

International Acquisition / Buyer

Mono Technology Public Company Limited

- Forecast film and TV series trend.
- Negotiate with international program suppliers.
- Work on contract and payment documentation.
- Summarize and manage all licensing progress.
- Support localization and marketing process.

May 2014 - Jan 2015

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Computer Science National Institute of Development Administration, Thailand	2018 - Present
Bachelor of Arts in Film Studies Thammasat University, Thailand	2005 - 2009
Liberal Studies LaGrange College, USA	2006 - 2007
AWARDS	
Georgia Rotary Student Program	2006 - 2007
Udacity Bertelsmann Data Science Challenge Scholarship Course	2018

LANGUAGES

- Fluent in Thai and English.

Udacity PyTorch Scholarship Challenge

- Intermediate level of German.

2018